const QUESTIONBANK = [ 
    {
      question: 'What is ethereum?',
      answers: [
        'A turing complete AI',
        'A cryptocurrency with a fixed price',
        'A programming language',
        'An open software platform built on blockchain technology'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'An open software platform built on blockchain technology',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is known as the creater of ethereum?',
      answers: [
        'Satoshi Nakamoto',
        'Vitalik Buterin',
        'David Chaum',
        'Craig Wright'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Vitalik Buterin',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'Which year was the ethereum white paper released?',
      answers: [
        '2013',
        '2009',
        '2014',
        '2008'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '2014',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'Which option best describes how ethereum might be used?',
      answers: [
        'As a computing platform for decentralized applications',
        'For validating bitcoin blocks',
        'For verifying transations, specifically for banks',
        'For buying lambos'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'As a computing platform for decentralized applications',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'What is an ethereum smart contract?',
      answers: [
        'An agreement between two bitcoin nodes',
        'An agreement between ethereum users and ethereum lawyers',
        'A digital agreement that is programmed to execute only if certain conditions are met',
        'An quantum computer running on solar and wind'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'A digital agreement that is programmed to execute only if certain conditions are met',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'What is an ethereum token?',
      answers: [
        'A cryptocurrency which always appreciates over time',
        'A digital asset built on top of ethereum',
        'A digital asset for investment only',
        'A J.R.R Tolkien collectable'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'A digital asset built on top of ethereum',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of ethereum\'s annual conference?',
      answers: [
      'Ethcon',
      'Devcon',
      'DevLearn',
      'The Puppy Bowl'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Devcon',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'Which option best describes how bitcoin and ethereum are different?',
      answers: [
        'Bitcoin is anonymous, but ethereum requires one\'s identity for use',
        'There is no difference',
        'Bitcoin miners earn ETH, while ethereum miners earn BTC',
        'Bitcoin is a peer-to-peer electronic cash system, Ethereum allows for scripts of code to be run as a global computational network'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Bitcoin is a peer-to-peer electronic cash system, Ethereum allows for scripts of code to be run as a global computational network',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'Where can you store your cryptocurrency, such as ETH?',
      answers: [
      'On a floppy disk',
      'In a digital wallet',
      'Typically always on a microchip embedded within your credit card',
      'In a piggy bank'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'In a digital wallet',
      icon: '',
      alt: ''
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the best way to learn more about ethereum?',
      answers: [
        'Visit ethereum.org',
        'Follow the ethereum community on \'crypto\' Twitter',
        'Find a local ethereum meetup or engage in a local Ethereum hackathon',
        'All of the above!'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'All of the above!',
    icon: '',
    alt: ''
    }
];
